Stan Lewis Collection of 45 rpm Records, 1965-1985 SC 48
Archives of African American Music and Culture
Stan Lewis Collection of 45 rpm Records
1965-1985
Archives of African American Music and Culture
Lewis, Stan, 1927-
SC 48
83 Audio Discs 45 rpm; 7 in.
Selection of 45rpm singles issued in the 1960s-1980s on record labels owned by Stan Lewis in Shreveport, Louisiana. Includes rhythm and blues, blues, and gospel music on Jewel Records and Stan's Record Division subsidiary labels Ronn Records, Paula Records, Susie Q Records, and Head.
Arrangement
Arranged in one series:
Series 1: 45rpm discs
Biographical / Historical
Stanley Lewis was born in 1927 in Shreveport, Louisiana. In 1948, he established Stan's Music Shop where he began distributing rhythm and blues records from independent labels. In 1954, he began producing R&B and Rock n' Roll records and by 1964, he founded and began releasing records on Jewel Records, soon followed by subsidiary labels, Paula and Ronn. The combined labels released over 1,000 releases over the next twenty years from artists usch as John Lee Hooker, Lowell Fulson, Soul Stirrers, and Ike and Tina Turner. During 1972, he sold over 2.5 million singles and over 470,000 albums. Lewis was inducted into the Louisiana Hall of Fame in 2009 and remained in Shreveport until his death in 2018.
Access Restrictions
Use of time-based media materials (audio and video) may require production of listening or viewing copies.
Access to streaming audio, moving image, and full resolution digital image materials may currently be restricted to researchers who can authenticate with an IU account or who are physically present on campus. Remote streaming to individual researchers may be allowed with the completion of applicable forms.
For further information about access to online audiovisual materials, contact AAAMC staff at aaamc@indiana.edu.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Stan Lewis in 1992.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains about eighty 45 rpm records from Stan Lewis' personal collection.
Rhythm and blues music
- 1. 45rpm discs
  - Anderson, Jesse -- Help Wanted; Send Me Some Loving C.O.D., 1972; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    Shelf Number
    7D 1
    Publisher
    Jewel Records
    Matrix Number
    SL-2138; SL-2139
    Catalog Number
    835
    Online Access
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/f46217t06w
    General
    Producer: Willie Dixon / Composer: Johnny Thompson; M. Booker
  - Benton, Buster -- Money is the Name of the Game; Good to the Last Drop, 1974; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 2
    SL-2449; SL-2450
    845
  - Benton, Buster -- Do it in the Rain; Sweet 94, 1978; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 3
    Ronn Records
    91
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/p58p38zs6r
    SL 2847
    Producer/Composer
    Producer: Ralph Bass; Composer: Buster Benton
  - Benton, Buster -- Born with the Blues; Lonesome for a Dime, 1979; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 4
    SL 2901
    93
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/f26811nv2s
  - Benton, Buster -- Love Like I Wanna; Sorry, 1980; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 5
    SL-2944
    95
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/069821jq1z
    Producer: N/A; Composer: Buster Benton
  - Benton, Buster -- Going Fishing; Spider in My Stew, 1985; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 6
    SL 3104 / SL 2356
    105
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/g25742cp7j
    Producer: n/a; Composer: Sain Eckford
  - Benton, Buster -- Cold Man Ain't No Good; The Feeling, 1981; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 7
    110
    SL 3188
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/w22v142c90
    Producer: Buster Benton; Composer: Buster Benton
  - Blake, Cicero -- School of Life; She's Cheatin' On You, 1980; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 8
    Paula Records
    SL 3140 / SL 3141
    448
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/j92g25b05n
    School of Life -- Composer(s): T. Tate, M.Gregory; Producer(s): Cicero Blake, Rico McFarland
    She's Cheatin' On You -- Composer(s): R. Jones, R. McFarland, C. Blake; Producer(s): Cicero Blake, Rico McFarland
  - Blake, Cicero -- Dip My Dipper; Be Good To Me, 1985; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 9
    Susie Q
    SU-333-A/B
    333
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/m01b593r27
    Producer: Bob Riley; Composer: R.S. Riley, Sr.
  - Brown, Charles -- Just A Blessing; Christmas in Heaven, 1970; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 10
    SL 1731-1732
    814
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/386019vd9f
    Producer: n/a; Composer: Charles Brown, Stan Lewis
  - Brown, Charles -- Merry Christmas Baby; Please Come Home for Christmas, 1970; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 11
    1733-1734
    815
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/p38w32tj7m
    Merry Chrismtas Baby -- Producer: n/a; Composer(s): L. Baxter, J. Moore
    Please Come Home for Christmas -- Producer: n/a; Composer(s): C. Brown, G. Redd
  - Brown, Charlie -- I've Got Your Love; I Just Can't Get Over You, 1973; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 12
    SL 2221-2222
    838
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/w22v142c7c
    Producer: B. Perry, E. Silvers; Composers: B. Perry, H. Hawkins, L. Dollison
  - Carr, Barbara -- Good Woman Go Bad; Messing With Your Mind, 1980; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 13
    SL 3142-3143
    449
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/s25x21ww2s
    Good Woman Go Bad -- Producer: Willie Mitchell, George Jackson; Composer(s): Harrison Calloway
    Messing With Your Mind -- Producer(s): Willie Mitchell, George Jackson; Composer(s): George Jackson, Robert Alton Miller
  - Carter Brothers -- Southern Country Boy; Booze in the Bottle, 1975; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 14
    SL 2533-2534
    745
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/g74q57qw89
    Prodcer: n/a; Composer: Duke Coleman
  - Cookie and the Cupcakes -- Mathilda; I'm Twisted, 1965; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 15
    SL 2164-2165
    221
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/r66j03gg8b
    Producer: George Khoury; Composer: G. Khoury, H. Thierry
  - Cookie and the Cupcakes -- Got You On My Mind; Sea of Love, 1979; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 16
    SL 3108
    446
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/257979x997
    Arranger
    Rob Smith
  - Dale and Grace -- I'm Leaving It All Up to You; Stop & Think It Over, 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 17
    SL 3077-3078
    444
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/h73p88ft6q
    I'm Leaving It All Up To You: Producer: n/a; Composer: D. Terry, Don F. Harris
    Stop and Think It Over: Producer: n/a; Composer: J. Graffagnino
  - Fred, John; Playboy Band -- Judy in Disguise (with glasses); Agnes English, 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 18
    447
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/g15b399n7d
    Producer(s)/Composer(s): John Fred, Andrew Bernard
  - Fred, John; Playboy Band -- Shirley; Harlem Shuffle, 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 19
    SL 3107-3108
    445
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/801p48vh28
    Producer: n/a; Composer: T. Bryan, John Fred
  - Fred, John; Playboy Band -- Judy in Disguise (With Glasses); When the Lights Go Out, 1967; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 20
    SL 1266-SL 1267
    282
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/h93g94m56b
    Producer(s): J. Fred, A. Bernard; Composer(s): J. Fred, A. Bernard
  - Frost, Frank -- Back Scratcher; Harp and Soul, 1966; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 21
    SL 1540-1541
    854
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/326m01dr4r
    Producer: Scotty Moore; Composer(s): F. Frost, C. Young
  - Fulson, Lowell -- I've Got the Blues; Change of Heart, 1981; 1 Audio Disc
    7D 22
    SL 3194-3195
    858
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/702q184v1b
    Producer: n/a; Composer: Fulson Lewis
  - Gilley, Mickey -- Now I Can Live Again; Down the Line, 1980; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 23
    SL 2965-2966
    437
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/k91f561p6t
    Now I Can Live Again - Producer/Composer: Jack Clement
    Down The Line - Producer: M. Gilley; Composer: Roy Orbison
  - Gilley, Mickey -- She Cheats on Me; You Can Count on Me, 1984; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 24
    SL 3053-3054
    441
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/f55z20w12p
    She Cheats on Me - Producer/Composer: n/a
    You Can Count on Me - Producer: n/a; Composer: Westmoreland Gostick
  - Gresham, Jesse (Plus 3); Parker, Robert -- Barefootin'; Shootin' the Grease, 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 25
    Head
    SL 1965-1966
    1050
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/c77s65kp0f
    Barefootin'- Producer: n/a; Composer: R. Parker
    Shootin' the Grease - Producer: A ClearSound Production; Composer: Jesse Gresham
  - Hooker, John Lee -- I Feel Good Pt. 1; I Feel Good Pt. 2, 1972; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 26
    SL 1981-1982
    824
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/2870894n0s
    Producer/Composer - Producer: Carson Records Paris; Composer: John Lee Hooker
  - Hooker, John Lee -- Stand By (Part 1); Stand By (Part 2), 1977; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 27
    SL 2801-2802
    852
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/742930f77q
  - Hooker, John Lee -- Roll and Tumble; Baby Baby, 1981; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 28
    SL 3154-3155
    856
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/s25x21ww05
    Producer: n/a; Composer: John Lee Hooker
  - Hooker, John Lee -- Dazie Mae; Hard Working Hanna, 1981; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 29
    SL 3226-3227
    860
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/316p98bs0h
    Dazie Mae - Producer: n/a, Composer: John Lee Hooker; Hard Working Hanna - Producer: n/a, Composer: Jimmy Reed
  - Hopkins, Lightnin' -- Back Door Friend; Fishing Clothes, 1968; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 30
    SL 1276-1277
    788
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/d37584137g
  - Hopkins, Lightnin' -- Wig Wearing Woman; Move On Out Pt. 2, 1969; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 31
    SL 1424-1425
    796
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/t05346gj1s
    Wig Wearin' Woman - Producer: n/a, Composer: Stan Lewis; Move On Out Pt. 2 - Producer: n/a, Composer: Hopkins Lewis
  - Hopkins, Lightnin' -- Lovin' Arms; Ride In Your New Automobile, 1969; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 32
    SL 1545-1546
    803
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/j43009zb80
    Producer: n/a; Composer: Lightnin' Hopkins
  - Hopkins, Lightnin' -- Play With Your Poodle; Breakfast Time, 1970; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 33
    SL 1602-1601
    807
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/z30p78jw70
    Producer: Don Logan; Composer: Sam Hopkins
  - Hopkins, Lightnin' -- I'm Comin' Home; You're Too Fast, 1970; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 34
    SL 1642-1641
    809
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/f85n303587
    Producer: Don Logan; Composer: Hopkins
  - Hopkins, Lightnin' -- My Charlie - Part 1; My Charlie - Part 2, 1970; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 35
    816
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/n49t055w54
  - Hopkins, Lightnin' -- Rock Me Mama; Love Me This Morning, 1971; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 36
    SL 1823-1824
    819
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/217q67mx6w
  - Hopkins, Lightnin' -- Found My Baby Crying; Uncle Stan the Hip Hit Record Man, 1972; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 37
    SL 1983-1984
    825
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/b19f16fh0t
    Producer: n/a; Composer: Hopkins Lewis
  - Hopkins, Lightnin' -- War Is Started; Dust My Broom, 1981; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 38
    857
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/069821jq0n
    Producer: n/a; Composer: S. Joseph
  - James, Elmore -- Dust My Broom; Gotta Find My Baby, 1966; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 39
    764
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/h83k91hv00
  - James, Elmore -- Make A Little Love; Catfish Blues, 1967; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 40
    SL 2140-2141
    783
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/n00989tf24
    Producer: n/a; Composer: James
  - Jeffrey S. Liberman Band; Johnson, King -- I'm the Man For Me; Where There's a Will There's a Way, 1985; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 41
    337
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/s25x21ww61
    Producer: n/a; Composer: Jeffrey S. Liberman, Bryon K. Bowie
  - Johnny and Jon -- Christmas in Vietnam; Why Did You Leave Me, 1966; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 42
    TM 1808-1809
    776
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/b29b19h75x
    Producer: n/a; Composer: John Wilson, F.R.Lewis, John Wessler
  - Johnson, Ernie -- You're About to Succeed; Give Me a Little Bit of Your Loving, 1985; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 43
    SL 3100-3101
    104
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/306s958m95
    Producer: n/a; Composer: E. Johnson
  - Johnson, Ernie -- Cold Woman; Party All Night, 1981; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 44
    SL 3186-3187
    109
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/178455bn1r
    Producer/Composer: Ernie Johnson
  - Johnson, Ernie -- Forever; Just In Time, 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 45
    SL 3230-3231
    113
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/762336k76x
    Producer: n/a; Composer: E Johnson, F. Pilate
  - Little Joe Blue -- My Tomorrow; Your Hands May Be Tied (But Your Heart's Got...), 1984; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 46
    SL 3059-3060
    99
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/8612679873
    My Tomorrow -- Producer: Bobby Patterson; Composer: Stan Lewis, Your Hands May Be Tied -- Producer: Bobby Patterson; Composer: J. Strickland, B. Patterson
  - McCall, Toussaint -- Nothing Takes the Place of You; Shimmy, 1967; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 51
    TM 1863-1864
    3
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/v83801s07r
    Producer: n/a; Composer: Toussaint L. McCall
  - McCall, Toussaint -- One Table Away; My Love Is a Guarantee, 1978; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 52
    SL 2859-2860
    26
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/r76f06jg4v
    Producer: n/a; Composer: P. Robinson, T. McCall
  - Memphis Slim -- I Wanna Dance; Born With the Blues, 1981; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 53B
    SL 3150-3151
    108
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/f55z20w041
    Producer: n/a; Composer: Memphis Slim, Peter Chatman
  - Montclairs -- Make Up For Lost Time; How Can One Man Live, 1974; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 54
    SL 2243-2244
    381
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/999n109f68
    Make Up For Lost Time -- Producer: Oliver Sain, Keith Fry, Composer: J. Strickland, B. Patterson; How Can One Man Live -- Producer: Oliver Sain, Keith Fry, Composer: Phil Perry
  - Nelson, Willie -- I Can't Find the Time; A Moment Isn't Very Long, 1984; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 55
    SL 3055-3056
    442
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/8515647655
    Producer: n/a; Composer: H. Cochran, W. Nelson
  - Neville, Aaron -- Tell It Like It Is; Why Worry, 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 56
    H 1049
    1049
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/n49t055w7r
    Producer: n/a; Composer: G. Davis, L. Diamond
  - Pastell, James -- Gone to Gilleys; Shining Star, 1980; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 57
    SL 2969-2970
    438
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/t15049jq83
    Gone to Gilleys -- Producer: n/a, Composers: Larry Kingston, Glen Sutton; Shining Star -- Producer: n/a; Composers: L. Graham, P. Richmond
  - Pastell, James -- Hell Yes I Cheated; Woman of the World, 1977; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 58
    SL 2803-2804
    425
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/z40k81mz2v
    Hell Yes I Cheated -- Producer: Glen Sutton, Composer: Glen Sutton, Larry Cheshier; Woman of the World -- Producer: Glen Sutton, Composer: James Pastell
  - Powell, Bobby -- The Bells; Bing Bong, 1985; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 59
    853
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/z60c87s39w
    The Bells -- Producer: n/a, Composer: J. Hicks; Bing Bong -- Producer: n/a, Composer: Lionel Whitfield
  - Powell, Bobby -- C.C. Rider; I'm Gonna Leave You, 1981; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 60
    SL 3152-3153
    855
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/m01b593r4v
    C.C. Rider -- Producer: n/a, Composer: Lionel Whitfield; I'm Gonna Leave You -- Producer: n/a, Composer: Lionel Whitfield, Jackie Johnson
  - Reed, Jimmy -- If You Don't Want Me Baby; I'm Leaving, 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 61
    SL 3244-3245
    862
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/t74c680106
    If You Don't Want Me Baby -- Producer: n/a, Composer: Jimmy Reed; I'm Leaving -- Producer: n/a, Composer: Mary Reed
  - Rush, Bobby -- Bowlegged Woman, Knock-kneed Man Pt. 1; Bowlegged Woman, Knock-kneed Man Pt. 2, 1972; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 62A
    SL 2128-2129
    834
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/d27880z50w
    Producer: Calvin Carter; Composer: Bobby Rush, Calvin Carter
  - Rush, Bobby -- Get It On With Me; Dust My Broom "Baby What You Want Me...", 1981; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 63
    SL 3224-3225
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/366613q70r
    Get It On With Me -- Producer: n/a, Composer: Bobby Rush; Dust My Broom -- Producer: n/a, Composer: Elmore James
  - Rush, Otis -- I Can't Quit You Baby; Groaning the Blues, 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 64
    SL 3242-3243
    861
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/534f65xg6w
    Producer: n/a; Composer: Wille Dixon
  - Taylor, Little Johnny -- Goin' to Get It On; When the Deal Goes Down, 1981; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 50
    SL 3148-3149
    107
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/p09623mg55
    Producer: n/a; Composer: Stan Lewis
  - Taylor, Little Johnny -- There Is Something On Your Mind; It's My Fault Darling, 1972; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 47
    SL 1970-1969
    59
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/g74q57qx4b
    There Is Something On Your Mind -- Producer: Miles Grayson, Composer: C.J. McNeeley; It's My Fault Darling -- Producer: Miles Grayson, Composers: M. Grayson, L. Horton
  - Taylor, Little Johnny -- It's My Fault Darling; I Ask Myself a Question, 1981; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 48
    SL 2981-2982
    97
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/851564764v
    I Ask Myself a Question -- Producer/Composer: Sonny Thompson; I Need Some Lovin' -- Producer: Sonny Thompson, Composer: W. Keyes, B. Bowie
  - Taylor, Little Johnny -- Just One More Chance; A New Song, 1980; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 49
    SL 3014-3015
    98
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/g15b399n8q
    Just One More Chance -- Producer: n/a; Composer: S. Thompson, V. Stampley
  - Taylor, Ted -- Miss You So; I'm Gonna Get Tough, 1967; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 65
    SL 1300-1301
    15
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/445c388n88
    Miss You So -- Producer: Gene Kent, Composer: M. Babb; I'm Gonna Get Tough -- Producer: Gene Kent, Composer: T. Taylor
  - Taylor, Ted -- I Need Your Love So Bad; Ollie Mae, 1968; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 66
    SL 1348-1349
    21
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/613m90h69p
    I Need Your Love So Bad -- Producer: n/a, Composer: H. Dunham; Ollie Mae -- Producer: n/a, Composer: Ted Taylor
  - Taylor, Ted -- Without a Woman; Honey Lou, 1968; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 67
    SL 1404-1405
    25
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/s25x21ww33
    Without A Woman -- Producers: Roger Hawkins, Jimmy Johnson, Composers: Dan Penn, Drew Miller, Quin Ivy; Honey Lou -- Producers: Roger Hawkins, J. Johnson, Composer: T. Taylor
  - Taylor, Ted -- Strangest Feeling; You Got to Feel It, 1968; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 68
    SL 1465-1464
    29
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/336h04gw39
    Strangest Feeling -- Producer: R. Hawkins, J. Johnson, Composer: Penn Oldham; You Got to Feel It -- Producer: R. Hawkins, J. Johnson, Composer: Beard, Le Flure
  - Taylor, Ted -- Long Ago; I'm Gonna Send You Back to Oklahoma, 1969; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    79D 69
    SL 1510-1511
    33
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/q87b78ws9n
    Long Ago -- Producer: Hawkins, Johnson, Composer: Dan Penn, Buddy Killen; I'm Gonna Send You Back to Oklahoma -- Producer: Hawkins, Johsnon, Composer: Ted Taylor
  - Taylor, Ted -- Houston Town; Cummins Prison Farm, 1981; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 70
    SL 3146-3147
    106
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/h93g94m53d
    Houston Town -- Producer: n/a, Composer: Andre Williams, Cummins Prison Farm -- Producer: n/a, Composer: Stan J. Lewis
  - Taylor, Ted -- Be Ever Wonderful; I Love You Just the Same, 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 71
    SL 3222-3223
    112
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/534f65xg2n
    Be Ever Wonderful -- Producer: n/a, Composers: J. Matyka, J. Scott, D. Robey; I Love You Just the Same -- Producers: n/a, Composer: Ted Taylor
  - Travis, Randy -- She's My Woman; All the Praises, 1978; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 72
    SL 2853-2854
    431
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/d27880z40m
    She's My Woman -- Producer: Joe Stampley, Composer: Jerry Van Tassel; All the Praises -- Producer: Joe Stampley, Composer: C. Tayler
  - Travis, Randy -- Dreamin'; I'll Take Any Willing Woman, 1978; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 73
    SL 2829-2830
    429
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/v13z80850s
    Dreamin' -- Producer: Joe Stampley, Composer: Ellis, DeVorzon; I'll Take Any Willing Woman -- Producer: Joe Stampley, Composers: Marvin Coe, Bob Bigger
  - Turner, Ike; Turner, Tina -- I Know You Don't Love Me No More; (I Know) You Will Always Be..., 1991; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 74
    SL 3232-3233
    453
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/w62f26bg4d
    Producer: n/a; Composer: Ike Turner
  - Turner, Ike and Tina -- I Know You Don't Love Me No More; (I Know) You Will Always Be My Baby, 1991; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 53A
    SL 3232
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/w82732gp0f
  - Turner, Joe -- Night Time is the Right Time; Morning Glory, 1969; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 75
    SL 1561-1562
    35
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/465544dw5w
    Producer: n/a; Composer: Joe Turner
  - Tuner, Tina -- Shake a Hand; Never Been to Spain, 1980; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 76
    SL 3145-3144
    450
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/h14970198n
    Shake A Hand -- Producer: Ike Turner, Composer: J. Morris; Never Been to Spain -- Producer: Ike Turner, Composer: Hoyt Axton
  - Uniques -- Not Too Long Ago; Fast Way of Living, 1965; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 77
    TM 1087-1086
    219
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/g15b399n35
    Not Too Long Ago -- Producer: Dale Hawkins, Composers: J. Stampley, M. Kilgore; Fast Way of Living -- Producer: Dale Hawkins, Composers: R.C. Stampley, Jack Rhodes
  - Uniques -- Please Come Home For Christmas; Please Come Home For Christmas (Instrumental), 1966; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 78
    TM 1824-1825
    255
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/069821jq3k
    Producer: n/a; Composers: Charles Brown, Gene Redd
  - Uniques -- All These Things; You Know That I Love You, 1970; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 79
    SL 1663-1664
    332
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/969z01332w
    All These Things -- Producer: n/a, Composer: N. Neville; You Know That I Love You -- Producer: n/a, Composer: J. Stampley
  - Uniques; Stampley, Joe -- All These Things; You Know That I Love You, 1976; 1 Audio Disc 45 rpm; 7 in.
    7D 80
    417
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/613m90h733